Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag, up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure, nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep
believing in our dreams.
And let our heart lead the way.
Then once we got all that,
all there's left is to go.
When we face the dark and stormy weather?
Keep the pace, we'll
link our hearts together.
Then I'm sure we'll make it through.
No matter what!
Keep running along, keep running along.
Still raising our flag as we journey on.
Though our chances are close to none.
We won't back down from anyone.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
Toward our own dreams
while keeping the pace.
With a compass pointing to our goal.
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world.
Start me up.
Keep running along, keep running along.
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top.
There's no way that we'll ever quit.
We'll keep heading for tomorrow.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase.
I see through your eyes,
what we'll have to face.
All the memories will stay in our hearts.
We'll never let them go, brand new world.
Let's start me up!
Huh?
What?
You're telling me we're on
the hunt for two keys now?
One for Robin and those two bozos?
Yeah, exactly.
How stupid can this get?
All right, at least I know
how deep of a hole we're in
You've really got me fired up now
Oh, boy.
He just won't stay down. Talk about tough.
Oh, I'll show you tough.
Franky!
Destroyer cannon!
Maybe you shouldn't do it then!
Moron!
That won't work.
I'm a six powers master.
No bullet can move as quickly as I can!
It doesn't matter how much
you run around or how fast!
It's practically impossible
for anyone to escape.
my Franky Destroyer Cannon.
These aren't just any cannons, they're
loaded with tracking cannonballs.
Huh, tracking cannonballs?
Does he mean they're cannonballs that
can sense their target and track it down?
I've never even heard
of technology like that.
This guy's amazing.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
You mean all the tracking is done by you?
How can you still run that damn fast?
Why am I letting this idiot
chase me around like this?
Oh, man, he disappeared again.
Come out!
Searching for me is pointless.
I'm a master of the shave technique.
With its power, not only am I
faster than the speed of lightning,
I'm also completely silent.
Just like an owl,
patiently hunting its prey.
I ALWAYS carry out a
flawless assassination!
Just like an owl, huh?
Precisely!
My target doesn't realize I'm upon
them until the moment of their death!
He was hiding over here!
Yeah, all that bragging
was real stealthy of ya.
Cocky jerk!
How dare you humiliate me like this!
No one humiliates CP9 and labs!
Shit!
Iron Ball!
Whoa, be careful!
Damn it, we're over the ocean!
This is bad.
The current's too strong.
It'll drag him straight to the waterfall.
There's nothing I can do
to help him in the sea.
Franky!
Swim with all your might!
Cha-ba-ba.
No matter what, I'll be fine.
I'll just use my moonwalk if I go over.
Not good.
I can hardly move.
I've got a damn strong current,
and I'm gonna run out of air.
I'm doubly screwed here. Cha-ba-ba.
Just hurry up and drown.
You're good!
There's no way.
He busted out of the fridge?
Thank you!
I am so full!
Holy crap, he got fat!
You cannot be serious!
Did you eat every piece of food in there?
I really don't have any
desire to die today!
I'm already at the base end!
Don't fall!
Don't fall! Don't go over!
Rick! Butterfly!
Cha-pa-pa-pa!
You are going over that
waterfall! No more!
Solid pace!
Ugly bastard!
Weapons left!
Eat this! Ha! Paper art!
Come on!
What the hell was that?
So close!
Too bad!
Damn it!
This is serious!
I've got to get to shore pronto!
One liter cola cannon!
Udaboo!
Joppa!
Didn't learn your lesson, huh?
It takes more than strength
to defeat a six powers master!
Strong hammer! Keep her off!
Now fall over the edge!
Strong right!
Let's go!
Let me go, you jerk!
I can't do the moonwalk with one
foot when I'm carrying someone else!
You're gonna make us fall!
Yeah, I realize that.
Tell you what, I'll let go of your lane.
After you've taken me back to shore.
We can fight it out on land.
Or you can put all your
energy into fighting
me right now and see where that gets us.
I prefer the first option.
But if I'm going down those
falls, you're coming too.
You and me, we're in the same boat here,
so why don't we just go back to shore?
Good job, that's some fine kicking.
Good, good.
Almost there. Keep at it.
Chubba-ba, just so you know, this battle
is gonna end as soon as we're there.
Oh, is that a fact?
Cause I just remembered a
little technique of mine.
That's sure to finish
you off in a single blow!
How funny?
That makes two of us, Fukuro.
So, what's your plan now?
Just take me to shore already.
I wanna hurry up and knock you
out and get this over with?
That's it!
I'm sick of your talking Sick of it!
I'm gonna shut you up right here and now!
Super cartwheel, fire and fall!
I'm going to slam you into the
tower and smash you to pieces!
That's your plan?
Well, that would pulverize
me, gotta give you that!
Franky, center!
I've got both your legs.
As long as I've got you bound
like this, you can't move around.
That doesn't mean anything!
At the speed we're going, there's
nothing you can do to slow us down now.
Let's just see about that.
70-millimeter caliber cola cannon.
Just a little coot-a-bomb.
He thugs our momentum.
We're not even rotating anymore. Damn you!
That's far enough.
We're right above the shore.
Now take this.
70-millimeter caliber,
1.5 bats, Call power!
Kaido! Stop it!
What are you trying to do?
Just give up already, you bastard!
Kaido! Bum!
Super!
Where the hell is that number two key?
Sorrel, I'm finished!
I'm too tired!
Give me a piggyback! No way!
Tempest kick!
Finger pistol!
What was that for?
Don't play innocent with me!
You were just pretending
to fire that kick at them.
You were aiming for me, weren't you?
That's the most paranoid
accusation I've ever heard.
But I will admit, you have
been getting in my way.
So if you want to fight, I'm ready.
What'd you say?
You've been getting in my
way, you stupid herbivore!
What are you talking about?
I like meat just as much as the next guy.
Wow!
I've always wondered about this.
You too, Zoro.
Didn't you just ask me the other day who
you think is stronger, a giraffe or a wolf?
The fact is that wolves
aren't much more than cunning.
But beyond that, they aren't exactly
the most capable of creatures.
You bastard.
That's the final straw.
So you want to do this right now?
Excellent. Let's go.
That kind of distraction won't last
long enough for us to get away.
What?
Well, I sure hope you have
some sort of backup plan then.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Whoever loses.
has to chop off his own hand.
That is the most terrifying
idea I've ever heard!
I'm not done explaining, just listen.
The first thing we do
once we get these cuffs
off us is run like hell
until we find Chopper.
With his medical expertise,
he'll be able to sew the hand back
on in no time at all, understand?
We're not ragdolls!
Don't be ridiculous!
Wait.
I've got another plan to
get us out of this mess.
I don't even want to hear it!
We won't be able to settle
this with words alone.
I'm ready to go when you are.
And let's up the stakes.
The winner gets to keep
the prey all to himself.
What the?
All right, Sniper King,
just hold that posture.
You are now a sewer.
Someone get me a lawyer!
There is no way I am not going
to sue your ass off for this!
Yo-yo!
Ugh.
I don't think I've ever seen
anyone with so little self-control.
You gained all that weight
in just a few minutes?
Thank you for your concern, but I'm...
I... I...
I...
Who said I'm concerned about you?
Okay, I get it.
You're just fine.
Don't talk with food in your mouth.
I'm just fine.
Yes, thank you.
That is indeed what I was trying to...
I don't know what you're
trying to do, but stop it!
You're okay, I'm okay, everything's great!
Now get back here!
Ah, yes, yes, of course.
Where was I again?
I shall solve this shortly.
Now observe.
My life returns!
Digest!
Absorb!
Complete!
What?
What the heck are you?
What did you just do?
I mean, could you do it again, please?
A life return!
The Digest!
That comes off!
So awesome!
How do you do that?
Well, how kind of you to ask!
A thousand years at sea, a
thousand years in the mountains,
breathing in the wind, than
drinking the morning dew.
I lived as a hermit to
complete my training, and lo,
at long last, the secrets of life
return revealed themselves to me.
From your head down to your toes,
every inch of the human body?
can be controlled with
the strength of will.
Why, you can even command your internal
organs and each hair to its very tip.
Using the mind to control
the workings of the body.
I've read about something
similar in a medical journal.
They called it biofeedback.
Then you're able to move your hair around
like an octopus because of that power?
Oh! Yo-yo!
An octopus?
How rude of you!
I am, as you say,
a CC!
A valiant lion, in other words!
Octopus, lion, whatever.
Life return!
And hair bite!
Yo-yo-yoy!
Oh, no!
If I get caught by his
hair, it's all over.
Where'd he go?
Finger pistol!
He did that with a blunt stick?
Iron body!
What is the matter?
Damn it. I thought so.
Unless I can hit him with arm point or
horn point, he's not going to budge.
But the rumble balls are powerful.
One in six hours is
about all I can handle.
Any more than that will put
too much strain on my body.
Even worse,
if I take another, I might not be able
to control my transformations anymore.
If I still can't win and
I have to take a third,
I might completely lose consciousness.
Is it worth it?
I don't think I could
damage him without it.
I shall skewer you and roast you alive!
Chess, come on!
I don't have time to think this over.
Rumble!
It's a risk, but it's the only
chance I've got to do or die.
One way or another, I have to
settle this in three minutes.
Take this!
Harpoin!
Shishikabob!
Take this!
Jumping point!
Wrong one!
Yo-yo-yay!
Ah, yo-yo-yay.
Damn it.
Just like I thought.
My transformations are messed up.
All I need is to get to arm point.
One shot with a cloven
hoof should be enough.
If this fire keeps spreading,
I'll end up suffocating.
I can't waste time fighting this
guy when he doesn't even have a key.
That's right.
I have to find key number two.
Zoro and Sniper King are counting on me.
We can't save Robin without their help.
Robin, hold on.
I won't let you down.
I'm here to save my friend.
And I'm not going to let
anybody get in my way.
You're a stubborn beast, aren't you?
Life return!
his hair is pointing at me who cares I
don't have time to think I have to win